my name is kolina and I'm a functional
consultant trainee I'm proud of being
part of the res skill program it gave me
the opportunity to start learning
business Central that is the start of a
really great journey for me my name is
Miguel I was a management assistant for
a Potter Factory and then I decided to
move on and try to rkill myself in this
res skill program I'm loving it my name
is Karina neelson and I'm the CEO of Cs
CS decided to enter the rescale program
with Microsoft because we needed a way
to scale how we can add people to our
business in the ecosystem today we have
two little Dynamics talents and one of
the biggest challenges is that you can't
just keep hiring from other partners so
what we see is that we have to get some
new blood into the channel we need
people that have more Consulting skills
with AI and with co-pilot there is going
to be
less development in the future so we
definitely need people that have more
understanding of business
processes I think this is a great
program for people that want to change
their lives and find meaningful jobs
without the training program sometimes
it can be a bit overwhelming because
there's quite a lot to learn to actually
have a path and to know that you know
you're supposed to do this this and this
it becomes much easier I thought that
changing Fields was going to be a really
long and hard task but it was actually
quite easy the first days were really
scary when we start the program
everything was starting to make sense
you have excellent coaches a great team
supporting you you have an excellent
Community behind you my name is Darren
treski and I'm the chief technology and
Innovation officer for Clos the unique
value ads of the reskilled program are
twofold one is training in soft skills
and the other is training in business
Consulting skills it's a program that
walks a student through it Case by case
process by process in a methodical way
and accelerates their skills at the
fastest Pace our experience working with
the BC Talent team so far has been great
the value from what we pay for the res
skill program is definitely paying off
it would be much more expensive if we
had to do all of this ourselves I enjoy
working with this
[Applause]
people